sunbeltrentals.com 2018-08-12

# Privacy Policy Statement - United States

Welcome to the Sunbelt Rentals, Inc. (“ **Sunbelt Rentals** ”) website (“the  **Site** ”). At Sunbelt Rentals, we are committed to respecting your privacy and to protecting any information you provide us. Accordingly, our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using Sunbelt Rentals website. Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy and our [Terms and Conditions of Use](https://www.sunbeltrentals.com/about/terms-and-conditions/) before using or submitting information to the Site.

  1. **Collection of Information** : In order to enhance consumers’ experiences when visiting the Site, we collect the following types of information as users browse the Site: 
    * **Personal Information.**  We may ask you to submit personally identifiable information (“ **Personal Information** ”) such as your name, address, email address, telephone number or credit card number to us via the Site. Some of this Personal Information is required in order to allow you to use all of the features of the Site. Other information is submitted by you voluntarily.  
 
    * **Anonymous Information.**  As you navigate through the Site, we may collect and store anonymous information (“ **Anonymous Information** ”) about you using various technologies such as cookies, Internet tags and navigational data. Your browser automatically transmits some of this anonymous information to us, such as the URL you just visited, the browser version your computer is operating, the date and time you visited, the pages you visited on the Site and your IP address. “Cookies” are tiny alphanumeric identifiers that are stored on your computer and allow us to adjust the Site to meet your personal browsing preferences. If your browser is set to refuse cookies, you may not have access to all areas or features of the Site.
  2. **Use of Your Information:**
    * _Anonymous Information_. We may aggregate, evaluate and use Anonymous Information to improve the Site and our business, and we may provide it to third parties. We may use cookies, IP addresses or other Anonymous Information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track customer site navigation and gather broad demographic information.
    * _Personal Information_. Gathering Personal Information about our customers allows us to serve you better. We will not use your Personal Information in a way that is prohibited by applicable law. Here are some ways in which we might use your Personal Information: 
      * Our Business Purposes. We may use your Personal Information for our everyday business purposes, such as to provide services to you, to market our products and services to you and to maintain your account with us. We may also share your Personal Information with third parties with whom we have joint marketing arrangements to market other products and services to you. Additionally, we may share your Personal Information with companies related to us by common ownership or control and they may use your Personal Information for their everyday business purposes.  
 
      * Service Providers. From time to time, we may employ companies and individuals to perform certain services on our behalf (such as conducting audits, performing legal services, processing credit card payments or providing customer service). These third-party service providers may have access to Personal Information, but only to the extent required to perform their assigned roles and they may not use your Personal Information for any other reason.  
 
      * Business Transfers. As our business continues to evolve, we may wish to sell or buy subsidiaries or business units. In such transactions, customer information (including Personal Information) generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the terms of any pre-existing Privacy Policy.  
 
      * Compliance with Law. We may release Personal Information about you if we believe such a release is necessary to comply with the law or in response to a subpoena or other legal process.
  3. **Protection of Your Information** : To prevent unauthorized access to, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place commercially reasonable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. However, no security system is perfect, and we cannot guarantee that information you provide to us over the Internet will remain private. We also cannot guarantee that information you transmit to us over the Internet will not be intercepted.
  4. **Opting Out of Promotional E-mails** : If you decide for any reason that you no longer wish to receive e-mail information from us, you can unsubscribe from the Site’s e-mail distribution list by clicking the “unsubscribe” link located at the bottom of each promotional e-mail. Your e-mail address will be removed from this Site’s email marketing list within 7 business days. You can also opt out of receiving promotional materials by notifying us by mail, telephone or e-mail at the address and number listed below:

          Sunbelt Rentals

          2341 Deerfield Drive  
          Fort Mill, SC 29715  

  5. Changes to this Privacy Policy: The Internet is constantly changing, as is the nature of our Internet business operations, so we will likely need to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. You should check this Privacy Policy frequently to review the latest version of the Privacy Policy. Our posting an amended version of the Privacy Policy on the Site will serve as notice to you of that amendment.  
 
  6. How to Contact Us: If you have any questions, requests or concerns related to this Privacy Policy, please email us at [customerservice@sunbeltrentals.com](mailto:customerservice@sunbeltrentals.com).  

Last updated: February 28, 2013
